We're going to meditate, so please
get ready to meditate.
[Music]
And yesterday we had a good class with all
the volunteers. I do
n't know if you saw the pole out there,
but there are about 200 volunteers
here working very, very hard,
and I'd like to give them some recognition.
[Applause]
What was the topic we covered yesterday? Have you
forgotten?
We talked about impossible things,
like when you have a fight with your
husband in the kitchen.
That husband is impossible. And a gene
nightgown, and the feather comes from me
because I have a seed in my mind.
To see, the dog doesn't have it, that's why it's
a dog.
If the seed makes you a dog or makes you
human, then I have some
feather seeds in my mind.
Who put the feather seed there? And only
you can put it there. You can't give
seeds to other people. It's not possible.
How did you put the feather seed there?
You gave feathers to other people. When you see,
take it to open it, a seed is put in
your mind.
And yesterday we had three questions in the
Heart Sutra class.
What does "device" say?
We had a Heart Sutra class
yesterday, and I asked them three questions. They
know the answers, so they can't
say.
I have a feather in my hand. There is a feather
in my hand.
There is a feather in my hand that comes from my
house because I gave to a feather. Now,
difficult question:
there is a feather in my hand that comes from the
feather.
What is the name of that?
Now, interesting. So,
the person who truly understands
emptiness is going to
give things to other people. That is
a sign that this person understands
emptiness. They are kind to everyone. They
smile at everyone. They
give things to everyone
because they understand emptiness.
This morning
we are going to do a Lion Dance meditation.
[Music]
I spoke with Aldo and they
told me how far they got in the
meditation,
and we are going to go further.
We are going to go through the eight levels.
We are going to go up the elevator and we are going to
get to the ninth floor
and we are going to meditate about our
teacher. Any teacher in your life.
Who is your first-grade teacher? Your
first teacher? Your mom? Your dad?
Then you have a teacher at
school and then a teacher at
work. Then you have your wife who is a
teacher to you too.
Then you have your children.
Maybe you have a spiritual teacher.
But in this meditation  We're going to ask
three questions. Number one,
there is a teacher in your mind.
2.
There is a teacher in your mind that comes from
your seeds.
3.
There is a teacher in your mind that doesn't come
from your seeds. It's
not impossible.
In the session,
I want to be in a white sky state to
sleep.
3.
You know, don't be
in Miami.
If you're in the countryside, I'll get it. It's
not an edition. If
you're a good person, if you understand
emptiness, you're going to give things to other
people. If you do
n't understand emptiness, we're
not going to give things to other people. If
you understand emptiness, you respect the teacher
that comes from you. You
respect the teacher, so it's a
seed for a teacher.
So the teacher goes
in meditation
or distinction.
All the teachers, your parents, these
teachers from school,
the person who taught you your trade, so we're going to
respect them.
You make a new seed so that it takes
this and stays with you. Let's begin.
Clear your throat,
really, in your ass.
We're meditating in a group,
so be careful. Try to be
quiet. We're going to meditate a little more.
This morning,
position yourself, so this can be a
comfortable position.
Normally in a meditation, we start
by observing the breath.
In this meditation, we're going to  Start by
observing the air conditioner
with your mind on the sound of the air
conditioner.
Don't forget the
special breathing for meditation. When you exhale
and finish the installation,
then push a little more air
out.
Understand,
then you will never be nervous
during meditation.
I listen to the air conditioner
[Music]
A fisherman.
Now go to your heart.
Listen to the heartbeat.
We are just observing the heartbeat.
White in Santander.
Now let's go inside the heart,
and the heart beats around us.
Inside the heart, it is not a
damp and dark place; it is
a very beautiful room with
lots of sunlight.
Remember the special breathing;
extra exhalation
is better.
Now let's go to the center of the heart,
and the sound seems to be far away.
Now let's put our mind on a grain
of sugar.
From the outside, they look very small,
but when we put our mind inside, it
is a very comfortable meditation room
with lots of sunlight.
Now expand my mind as wide
as the Pacific Ocean
crossing the whole world.
Remember to do the extra exhalation.
Now we add the blue sky.
My mind stretches from the bottom of the
ocean to the blue of the sky.
Okay,
now we decide to turn off the mind,
like when we turn off a light.
If a thought comes to mind,
block it.
Remember the extra exhalation
in this sentence.
Now, if
thoughts or images come to mind, just let them pass. Do
n't fight them.
Now we're ready to begin
meditation.
Please choose one of the teachers
in your life,
maybe your mom or dad, a
school teacher, or a
spiritual teacher.
Ask them gently to
come and meditate with you. They're
not pictures; they're real people.
They're breathing
what's happening to you. They're
looking at you with love
and a smile because you're meditating,
and they know it will help you.
So bring the teacher to sit
next to you.
If you have a pen, stand to the
side
and let them sit.
Think of something you really love about
this teacher, a quality they have,
like patience or working to
help others.
Then the teacher is like the pen,
and the quality I see in them is
coming from me.
So I must have planted a
seed for that
in my past life.  The
law of karma
says that the seed must be similar to the
result,
and if my teacher is very patient,
I must have been very patient in my
past life.
If my teacher is very helpful to
others,
I must have been very helpful to
another being in past lives.
So let's take a journey to our
past lives and just imagine where I
lived
hundreds of years ago, what
my job was, what I
looked like (
male or female), what
my family was like,
and what I did that makes me see
this teacher as so beautiful. Now, you
are free in this part of the
meditation to create a beautiful story.
Don't be afraid to make a movie,
and you are the hero of the movie.
Let's spend some time here and enjoy
it.
Sometimes you will get distracted to think about
food,
tension, and become moderate,
but slowly return to the meditation. For a moment,
the scale you have set.
Now, please return to your teacher
and again enjoy these beautiful
qualities within them.
You can ask these three questions:
Number 1: Does
my teacher have this beautiful quality? Does
this beautiful quality come from me?
And number 3: Does this beautiful quality come
from itself?
And the answer is no.
conventional
and that's careful
if my teacher has emptiness
then I can keep my teacher in
my life
when I go home
if I share with other people
who are interested
gently
then plant the seeds to see
my teacher stay with me
nothing is compact
now let's go back down the levels
respectfully we tell the teacher
that we are going to leave the meditation
and go to the eighth level
event
the mind has images and thoughts
but I ignore them
in it I
am very silent the mind maybe
is talking but I don't hear it
a multitude of extraction
remember to do the extra exhalation
at the end of each breath
now let's go to level 7
if the mind thoughts come to the
mind the blocks to keep the
mind silent
i
on sky I
still don't bring my mind back to the
sky and the oceans we already
have it the ball
now only to the very deep oceans
now very gently inside the very small grain
of sugar
to the cut of the extra exhalation
now to the center of the heart
the heartbeat is heard far away
in health
now the walls are the heart and it has it
close to me
now return to your body and just observe
your heart
and
exc the  scammers also to you
now observe three long breaths
to close the meditation
and open your eyes stretch out
uy it
's from playstation martinez it's
and
although
inditex
in negative that are called laws of
action m tasks and demand m 10
are of six years remains in the brush
positioning this is a new idea
at the beginning
what is it called they want to see how
john ging linguist laghman tennis line does
n't sound like my Chinese
they taught me Chinese
and then I tell it to my Chinese friends
and they look at me with a face of to
the sands
then
in the language it is written
when we are born that we care we do
n't have a body and a mind
and you go to rent a car
paid and they give you a car it's not the same
when we are born and a good touch you have a
car that in rent they have
because I didn't say you buy a car
now because you have to return it get
what advantages it
is temporary it is a rent that we don't have
this body of the disc the line this
body is cold at this moment or
very hot shoots this body gets
hungry
in itself
the smoke
I have a friend who said he was never going to
eat animal and one day he was very very
hungry and all the friends were
eating fish
then she also ate the fish
without design and she decided to be
vegetarian but one day she was very
hungry
and there was no other food
so finally she ate the fish shop
when you rent this car body
you are going to do bad things to take care of
this car the club because this car
is not very good
this car needs food 2 or 3 times
a day
this car needs a sweater
this car needs many things
in 19 months
everyone in this room is a good
person name I like to distinguish
no one would steal anything here
the places in the world where there's
fire of the type there are very few places in the
world where there are 500 people
and you can leave your bag here and no one is
going to take it
everyone is Buddhist
but if someone really needs
the money their mom is sick their
children are starving and they will
take it several or all I would too
warsame we are the same as her daughter
we have this car in rent
so we try to be good
we try not to hurt others but
fixing full but if we don't have food
very sad we are going to steal the decision
live is human nature son world
youtube twitter we are going to steal to
feed this body
fan  From scanner life with Granada along
with Nextel, then from this type of life
we're going to have another rental car in the
next life so big that they
obey you,
but that car is also going to be of this
type.
This is not a market test, it's an
old American car
and all because they're always
breaking down and it needs a sweater, it needs
food, it
needs to go to the bathroom. It's
not a very good car, and inside it
has blood and flesh and bones.
5000 important training parts for
Gianmarco to learn, and they're not cooperating.
The rules,
Lance Lynn, install the lungs. They're
fighting against the heart of the
vanguard. The lung wants more. The
abyss with the heart needs more heat,
so they're fighting one when it
tries Sunwing. If the lungs win, the
old ones get cold.
If the heart,
we have trouble breathing.
Lack of awakening. Fighting edition. 5000
parts are losing to each other. I
translated for a traditional doctor.
Strength for many years
from within is 50,
and he said one interesting thing:
when the lungs and heart are
in balance, the year is unusual
for a healthy person. The new is not
normal. If by the same, a
sick person is normal.
Health  It's temporary in itself since I only
had a form and it cut even with people
so to have it alive and even
good people if we didn't have
food in this hotel
[Music] we would steal
food
to keep us alive in the
world in war everyone
does things right well then
when we die feeling full for having
stolen the food
we're going to have this same body again
one way reveals here on one side
this body has many now we have
a car in order but it's not a very
good quality cool because we've done
bad things to get this body
we have a body like this
and we have we have to work in
don't give it with you and if we don't have
food we're going to steal if we steal
nectar very toys for the next
life we'll have a body like this
again body steal and steal bar and
melee steal and steal but if in your
circle of distance
this is widened Russians so healthy
we have to get out of samsara we have to
change this body and if you see the emptiness
directly then from the inside
the body will start to change because in
it there are tests and then after that you're not going to
Having a body like this means you'll have a
better body, a body
that doesn't need to eat and won't hurt
others to get food. Then it will last
forever.
That body is very good, it's very cool.
Look, if you have it, you can help
people in many cities at the same
time. It's a very efficient body. I don't age.
It's the ex-cop. That's really
a test. The model for the moment
allows it, and the rent is permanent.
Once you have it, you don't have to return the queen.
Oh my, oh my, the one from Paris.
Now we have a defective body, and
we have to change it. We have
to change it with... Wait until the time to
go back up on. Don't wait until it's
time to return the car to the
airport.
While you're young, see the beat,
the work, the other things in your life. It's
not an emergency.
Thames Valley.
Changing the body is an emergency.
We have to do it now, and the best
way to do it is emptiness. Davis
thought, Mestral Mancusi. That's why we spend
so much time in emptiness. Okay, go the
line.
Pi-pi-pi,
White Feather 6. I
know you have it in the bathroom. I hope I'll tell
my love teacher,
like, the termination. Very well.  In the
multiple attempt, how did I live positively
because this body was created by
bad seeds? We always have problems, it's always
going to be hungry, it's
not a very good body. I take advantage of
my soul, it's in things that
we had to be relevant, that they have to
have
and benefits before Israel.
Even if you don't have a disease right now,
maybe there is some
disease, we don't know, maybe we already
have cancer. If we don't
know it yet, it doesn't come out, it's
okay. We don't
have a life that has cancer, we
think that now it is dying and we
are all surprised. Another one, you were in
class
last month, you looked very good.
[Music]
The cancer was growing but we didn't
know that I had it. Even if right now you
feel very good, don't
worry, you are going to feel bad later, it is
the nature of this body.
Before, we have to change it, now what about the ones that
people who have
100 contribute and also maintain that they maintained on
the street? I had to try, Txepetxa, it
shoots up, they make up this body, it came from
marking more and
to keep it alive
we do Valgarma in these tricks and it is a
circle formed in the Congo
of curves and Sonia's whereabouts in sanction,
then we are  In samsara, if
you work, things are only two causes. For
classes, world, go to these two things. Now
our class will go to those causes.
We will talk about the two causes.
Number 1: bad seeds. There are
two bad seeds that make this
body like a feather. The body and the
feather are the same. This also comes from
me.
This also comes from my Walmex, from this, which
makes this body defective. And I
have two things:
my bad karma
from the past, maybe
with my afternoon in my past life. I
invite you to sleep, and then playing
because of my faults, they killed an animal
different from the queen. Something very bad
is happening in China right now:
more than 10 million chickens in China
every year, and 10 million.
And each support also has a crow, and they
also want to be alive like
us.
And when you go somewhere, like
the French fries, ate the salad,
but since it's a human arm, what?
And some scientists have discovered
that meat has poison inside.
What is it called
when you have too much fat in your
blood? Cholesterol.
The biggest source of cholesterol is
meat,
and 65% of people in the US eat
and they  It gives cholesterol, it
goes
and 400,000 people die every year
because of this,
this doesn't form
[Music]
they can make a green drink
in Mexico, you become healthy
and I think I became a vegetarian
40 years ago
from my friends, I'm walking and my friends
told me but you're not going to have protein, you're going to get
sick, you walk the
health and we're not going to be healthy
and they're all dead,
they understand that it lasted, what they don't need,
meat, they don't need it
with a filter outside of the type, it only causes
problems for other people and touch
are useful things of Spanish, two things
cause this body like the karma of
chromium that causes karma,
the law of internal that you have, both
also be Brady that doesn't have drive
more,
we inhabit strong things, chapter
4 of the book inhabit lean electric, see,
let's review the agreement, le lee
hitn system top show, what
is late and indesca, all the stars you
see in the sky, good of coal,
however you are bed, which is
coal,
that primary karma, the
most basic karma, which is the
thought when you think of digging,
Guayamerín pod  mini camera
right now we're doing a lot of karma or it's
cold I
have to go to the bathroom
slow
in three seconds
sampaio who reading three topics
thinking very famous thought is the most
basic karma the most basic form of
karma
and there is secondary karma
what it says is the water and what it does is
ok everything know
two disparate things and eat that causes of
this body
what we do and what we say
and what we do and think we are good
because of what we think
thinking camps one time for talking
thought comes a second before what
we say and a second before we
do something
we think something
or it's very cold but I have to tell you
already be the windows it jazzmen so
when you see yasmin youtube bar and how are
you going to do karma body
ready
so that's your karma body
too and then you're going to say
something
enjoy the cloud and she's going to say I
enjoy the class and you're going to do
if they emit happy everything good class the class
was very good for the Eskimos
it's like if the Eskimos came they would
enjoy it because in short as I am because of
thought comes  Just before
camps, because then comes the
talking about camping and making a face.
This is that bad
thinking, the mother of karma,
is thought. It's very disparate, and if
we want to understand who made this body,
how we make this body, investigating the
5, we need to understand the thought
that was located in spend the next.
So we're going to spend the next
three or four retreats with statisticians and
we're going to study the karma of the
thought that influences me and how
we can improve it. It
has Washington, Paris, and that's going to
change the body.
Okay,
let's take a break now.
Go do some exercise to
stay active. Song and festivals,
we'll be gone in 15 minutes.
Okay, it
's the 7 to 22 shift. It
can be a review of the last eight
years of hunger, so I'm going to do a
review with images, and I normally
do it in the afternoon,
but this afternoon we have another job.
We're going to have a fire, not a special fire,
in a primary Fosovi ceremony, and we're
also going to have three marriages,
which one...  The purpose of the mini fire
has two meanings. Number one, the pub
or Beckham, where we take our bad things to the
Miguel Wind fire.
During the fire, we never
put karma as an offering;
we sell it to the fire, and the oldest iftar is burned.
If there is a bad seed in your past,
in your life, and we have all done it, I did it
too, I,
Ivanovic. If I tell you what I did
when I was young, it would be commonplace. So
write it on a piece of paper,
and at the end of the fire,
we are going to throw the paper into the fire. And
during the fire, we are going to have
three fires.
If the teachers are very experienced,
some of them did
three-year silent retreats. We have several
teachers here who wanted the
three-year silent retreat,
some and some, but this one goes through it, and you
die, and so another one is Gadget
Michaels.
They are going to help us with the fire,
and they are welcome to put something
in the fire, and we are going to give them a dish
on YouTube. And I have a suggestion: take it and
put it in the fire. I have an idea:
don't do it like this. Here,
someone, do it with elegance.
Here, I have the idea, not the desire.
and that they can practice
that the law of
not so
and they're going to be helping them with
style with style
[Music]
the Chinese like Jamie very handsome
come here
good
in the 5
and think about this I throw there my
bad karma in what is the first
meaning of the offering of when you
can parties the Buddhas love it
when you confess the evaluation
never be afraid of how to tell that
master the worst thing you did
the happy are happy happy
that you're Aniston and I went to
Tokman you can cleanse those seeds if
you talk about it
so I threw it in the fire I did
a negative thing when I was
young when I was very young a long time ago
when I grew up and also yesterday
that you see be honest
I can too and that I the journey
of the artist
the Judases love the smell of this truth pleases them
softly it's
good to tell the master the good
seed that exists it's also good to
tell them the black thing and if that smoke
is very very sweet for them it has very
good Brooks reads it
and we're going to improve it and Shaman it takes time to
become a good person
we've been bad people for 10
million it's not going  It's changed in 12 years,
slow progress and many big
mistakes even now, so don't be
predatory, don't say anything and I'm a
bad person, it's true,
but they are improving little by little, that's
good, and it's
a figure, it rises and reaches the
Buddhas
and they know and they don't smell, oh how nice,
someone is burning their bad karma, it smells
good, I
say that smoke is going to reach the
whole world, the guy was going to bring peace
to other people,
500 people in Thailand are burning
their bad seeds
and that smoke is going to touch the world, the wind is going to
carry it everywhere and a
cool, happy guy was going to make
people feel happier, they are going to feel
happier, those are the two purposes of the game,
number one, burn,
number two, peace, you have to have,
if you are tired you don't have to
stay, it's been about two and a half hours,
if you feel that it was enough for
you
go to sleep and you don't have to
stay until the last minute,
we are going to have snacks, have fun,
life is very short, life is very
difficult,
if you are in Thailand you should enjoy it
during the fire,
the Buddhas  They like that they like that they
are happy.
The purpose of Buddhism is for you to be
happy, so while you practice
Buddhism, it's supposed to be
fun.
Gisela, I stayed for an hour. I enjoyed the
water fire with the White City in slip.
Now I want to go home to see you. I do
n't know in this type of Buddhist, each
user,
okay.
[Music]
Let's repair, let's review. Sorry
about the previous ones, that's a different one.
Hang in there,
you can teach that. It
gave me in the park with my heart. In
this development, it
can be a review of the part where it
says how to study in these topics.
In the image, there is a
person having coffee with
their friend. That is part of this program.
Go to the clear people class.
Listen to the class.
Art of class. After the class,
let's enjoy and have coffee.
The desserts are very good here.
I like to declare. There are 3
in the class. I drink green juice. Art
of class.
After the class, I'm going for a dessert
here. Damn, wow, I enjoyed it at the
convention in Ricote and talk about what you
heard in the class 3 times.
They institute it's the tradition with friends
with their friends Ischia King James no
light peace is probably checking
he no James beige milk
that you heard from the class that talked
about the rental car that he said I don't
remember that finally
with three or four to one is going to say I
was asleep during that part of the iof
on a motorcycle just like it is the observe I count
with him then your friend is going to tell you what he
said which is about the sheriff and
retired car James present if
you enjoy Jamie's presentation
[Music]
sometimes it's nice in the park I was
asleep urgently Samu of God then you re
spend it with some friends
this is an ancient tradition 2000 years
bye have coffee buy desserts don't
tell anyone
eat and discuss the key of that post
is very funny it
is very very important in Berlin so that you
remember it later this is
the tradition ok
next pictures next picture
my terms Mr. Nick already discal
this is called how to think about yourself
Mr. Mercer
thinks you are a sick person
signs thinks you have a disease
sign spiritually like cancer
spiritual inside Fink Valdés teaching
thinks about these teachings
tells me the fault is like medicine that
all the teachers are like
news doctors and that seeing online
all the teachers together are like the
medical staff
the medical staff and the teachings are
the medicine
maybe our body is not sick
but our heart is sick all
the time
when you come here I am taking
medicine
your friends ask you are taking
medicine and what kind of medicine I am
taking two or three times a day
to fix my mind my heart
our tradition of thinking you have to
come to class I am taking
medicine
and there is a doctor
Veselá is the little doctor doubt is the
director of the hospital of love that
report I am working to help
Quito Wilde Jasmine gay puppet this
way
people ask me why Jasmine
gave the teachers this white coat with
the according to Dr.
DT do you understand me for what
Textron what follows says to this opera
[Music]
well inquire into the opera of history they are
going to tell me the story of the
famous person
at 17 years old with me here today
with a marketing pig with the king of
the  Man, they're
going to tell a story about the types of
famous people who are alive,
vacant, keep some people with
mastery,
means listen to the opera,
cool, and he said because from Bombay in India they
invited him to go to India,
Deepak means to see the deer park,
this is where he returned, the first
teachings,
I'm very famous, you don't want to go to the
deer park, don't integrate, doesn't
mean to operate, there's no more herbal water, they
tell water, I do
n't want to hear about Johnson, I
want to feel it myself, I do
n't want to go to the
deer park and see where Buddha walked, where Buddha
walked 2000 years ago, how sad, Jr.,
I want to be here, study it, Marin, and
become a Buddha,
then they're going to think about me, they say, I
told you the tradition of the mind, I
must sing, do
n't come to Thailand to see a
statue of Lenin, I don't
know who he is or what
Mr. Lizard is, like full in
the bodyguard, great expanse, and they're going to
walk around shops, it's
very good to respect the
sacred places, additives, and it's good to read the
stories of the ancient saints like
Nagarjuna, famous with some times
and  Do it sometimes, but spend most of
your time in your practice and locate, and you
become an assistant, and let them
make a statue of you,
and let them sing, study, study
[Music]
I'm letting them tell their
story,
work on yourself, from Audi Place Tampa
Bay, in the sacred places of times, I
got them into House Roddick Ley, but make your
home a sacred place, people will come to your
house for 500 years. If you go in 500 years, she
was a normal, sterile person,
Einstein, then she studied the dance of the
elitist Kong, and then she saw emptiness. I
got Amparo's teaching on that day,
her body began to change, if my field,
and she became a Buddha in this house,
and people can walk around your
house,
no, no, time is passing, thinking about
the oldest ones. You're going to
walk around your house
for blessings, and it's true that maybe they
can charge because they walk around
your house.
If you want, it's a joke,
Whiting Hot
says Peter, postpone it, older.
This image should remind you when you're
sitting with your friends in the cafe, you
can talk, you can play the
picture game.  showing an image without
this is that person singing what
is the meaning of writing a
song about me after I
become a Buddha
way
where did they go and an injection or
Robert Neville of pans
since we need
and it's not fault estimate the resource of
life not only is he very busy
ok were the impressions to add
to your book I have to see and [ __ ]
please finish the biggest criticism and no
fault now can you take a picture
with your phone
camera emits
the picture I need the image
of the injection
how do you want Josh and don't forget that it's
your seed
there's a problem in the world today
500 years ago when he was taught he knew
penicillin and that nobody taking advantage of a
guy so you can't have surgeries
people died from
infection in the anus
I'll have Discovery Choices then
they discovered penicillin
from the projection so an operation
you put penicillin just like
infection you won't get infected
and you don't die
if you don't have penicillin it does
n't help and you'll possibly die are
nothing now now there's a problem in the
world Sanz publishes very different and
There are people who become
resistant to penicillin.
of that bacteria knows how to fight
penicillin.
For some people, the penicillin no longer
works.
The bacteria in their body adapted.
In an election year, now when
penicillins don't work because we're
talking about the Sardis
class itself, the purpose of this class
is to fight against negative thinking
in your own heart when answering,
and we're going to start a long list of
negative emotions.
Maybe there are 84.
It's very depressive, desire, anger, a very, very
long list. It has PP. It's ethical.
They have the purpose of coming to Thailand,
and I'm very confident. It's to learn with
those who commit crimes, with whom. The
main weapon is vitality and strength
to fight against those 84 old
measures. If your husband yells at you, do you
remember the index finger pen or what bell? You
tell me, okay, it comes from my child. If you
change it, your seed is me. Do
n't yell at your children. Don't make a
seed to yell at 25 to the fort. I
was teaching for 40 years.
Some of the students have been with me for
25 years, and recently someone came to me. It's
nothing that is  The Hague Whitman
Harper I have problems with my
husband this I have problems with my
husband do
you have a suggestion the fool is going to
tell me and don't tell me about the
seeds
listen to it a lot don't tell me ashes the
null of the seeds I don't feel anything
new arrives my system they have no
resistance to penicillin before they
became resistant to penicillin
you gave them and it was already a song
melted same and therapy for me today
the west wing camp you don't want me to
help you but you don't want me to tell you
the positions 10 minutes that I tell you
something new
[Laughter] I
couldn't think of something here I'm
sorry that you've been core web
had a nuclear weapon
and doesn't use it online and you want a
slingshot and I don't sell slingshots anymore I ca
n't teach you one small thing
buy a book at the airport Christmas
how to be happy with the husband from the
camp the husband who comes from the
husband you
can find him at the airport
how will the husband who comes from the
husband
talk to him all night and at the end of the year tell him
not to yell at him sorry Aaron
Cell I don't sell that's the price
I sell penicillin from YouTube no  These
customs
you can get free for times, although it's
three or four times
and you don't use it when you get back home and you're going to
stop listening, you're
not going to hear it anymore. The third time
is the fourth time, you're
not going to hear what I say. There are
videos, my very old student and the joke,
PP, when he lifted the pen, it starts
immediately. You can go to sleep,
tree
bolt. I'm at home. If you have trouble
sleeping,
well, friend, bring the pen.
So the first time you priest,
if you hear it three times and don't use it anymore, you're
not going to hear it anymore.
Apply it now. Sorry, don't keep
coming to Thailand
and say that you discovered it. You showed the
pen from last year because you show the
pen. Enter the funk and a half site
because you keep fighting against your
husband. They understand and scam and Diogenes. I
like it.
If you stop fighting with your husband, I'm going to
stop showing the pen. What does Wii
agree with? Ex-pitcher. Next
image
with management. When he was young, he kills.
If you look closely, maybe he has hair.
What is he doing in this image of
Stalin? Entity in seminar. Convinced.
You can see the dates. It was 11 years ago.  He's
raising funds for, and if he's like,
please, money,
we have to save the old books
because we're talking about this
Monday, and so, call after you
study weapons and a chasm, Tibiletti
has criminal responsibility, you have the
responsibility to keep it alive in the
world.
Sometimes you can see a map of all the
religions of the world,
Buddhism almost died with those books, they almost
disappeared.
I went to the airport,
they're selling their backs, the
diamond cutter, his after making little ones.
I went to study at the bar in Canada, Fama
Master, boss of a master, so of
ancient calligraphy that you want to learn
first,
and my family are experts of the
current INAH, we've done it for 15
generations, we've done Singer and Tommy,
the first karting, and he taught me the
first letters in Vienna, and I told him what
the meaning of this letter is, to honor, it was
n't given, Fama, joint you for fighting
in the family, he's drawn, it's sucking for
15, web idol, a thousand whys, but they don't know
the meaning,
all the age, don't be like that, keep
the book alive in the world
and keep the meaning alive, at the
point, we have to keep both,
and if Haiti can keep the book alive,
help, it takes away  mimicry, but you
have to keep the meaning alive,
which is your job, and you have to help.
How can you repair the Buddha's goodness?
Make sure the book doesn't disappear.
Every generation has a responsibility. The
kind of text environment we have to
keep the books and give them to the
new generations available, and this
is your responsibility. You want
after you come once more,
after you heard this. If
you heard the two husbands in the kitchen,
after that you have no
external booking responsibility to give the book to
the next generation. It will be the
next generation. I started in
Tunisia. My work ends two days later.
Your work starts.
You in the next generation, and
then your work will begin.
That is the job that every
generation has. You have to pass it on to the
next generation, otherwise it will
die.
Left
daughters.
This child, if he has the flu, is sick.
You are taking medicine. In fact, he
looks a little like I acquired Anatolia's son. He
is taking medicine. Or singing from the
English language, but he is also sitting in
the hunger class. 400 dollars. They
forge it in 1,400. Davor strike 100
dollars.
[Music]
We're in Queda Suárez, this area.
If anyone can guess what it is, in
Cheste, I'm going to
repeat it. You can tell me
now.
That's what does not mean, Spain. It's not true,
but it's just this
image.
The aspirin.
[Music] I
took it while I listen. You do
n't give the children medicine, but you
teach them emptiness. So you can
do both in the class, and
you deserve to use the medicine that it indicates
in the class, and also use the medicine
that everything elegant, or I take it. Don't
wait until you return home.
In this attitude of medicine, you
can start taking the medicine. You
have the class inside the class. You're
sitting next to someone, or you feel
cold. You feel cold in the class, and without
coaching, you're being taught your
nights, and without depending, you're being
taught the pen,
but you feel uncomfortable. By the way, we
turned off the air conditioning, but this
morning I was also cold,
balance, and King Kong. While I'm
teaching with zinc, emptiness, the pen
comes from Marín
because the team made it so cold. What's wrong with
you?
[Music] I
'm not  Taking the medicine during
class, understand that this mini is a
very deep meaning of deserving me
of the medicine and half key of the
multimedia game.
Don't walk two days and with the medicine in your
hand is the art of medicine. Take the medicine so
that you don't have it in your
bag. I'm going to use it when I
get home.
Use it in class
for me.
And who made the cold room this morning?
You
took the medicine during the night. I
saw Tim turning up the
air conditioning. Who created the team?
Understand well. Training the Disney High
testimony. The team turned up the air
conditioning very this morning. So he
argued, but who made the team
in class this morning? Use the medicine
immediately and even during
class. Apart from what you are being
taught about fire, we are going to
burn our bad seeds.
Write. Start writing now. I'm starting to
write on the paper right now.
Don't say, "I'll do it
when I get home." When I'm
eating,
do it now, but do it during
classes 10 and 20. Mercedes,
this means take the medicine
immediately. It is a tradition in the
hunger
that if  They're not going to be very busy, they're going to
the airport, they're going to be importing
these practices. Don't start the practice, do
n't say that the practice left tomorrow
morning, that before,
after the practice in this chair right now,
don't wait until tomorrow, that tsakiris
finishes
the meaning of the following background image
has extended to that Goldman,
this is not, nor do they sing defeat in real
tomorrow x with which I think it's going to be
if the fear of Beijing was taken out, hobby
walkers, it's already there, it's the motivation to
become a delicacy, index, we have
in this room another crisp one, and I don't know,
20 masters of heart
worked very hard and have studied for
20, 15 years,
Batista del Lago, but they started like
you, they added some rhymes, 30
years to the
hunger of my master, and they listened, they
practiced and became
masters, it's
a great honor
and it's very important that you
become the master, it's imposing, it's very
important to be, you should do it, it
might, Jean and Beat Cantillo, it's my dream
that he becomes the master, in
fact,
and I'll be ready later
when you  You become a teacher,
there are three things you have to be
careful about. Number one is money, and
people offer you money. It's
very good to deal with the margins and
transform money. It's useful.
'We're paying for the plane,
for the plane. This is just a
bridge, but it's not the most important thing about the
site. Ones family, what the teacher
wants from you, and if you practice this, practice, thing,
right now what you feel is cold in
Haiti and Dutch
[Music]
looking towards where the team is in English
if you do it like this and you look at the pen and
you turn to look at the air conditioning, it comes, it comes
from me, the
teacher feels happy, you're already
Turning on
Nicole from the end there was practice we call
the offering of your practice this is the
best offering
the happy happy
if you give money after this
class I
appreciate it but ask for compassion and next
if you come with me next year it's worth it
in Bali
since I came fighting match my husband
my husband and I fight much less
I hope it's perfect
10 million years you've been fighting you're
not going to change in a year don expect do
n't expect to choose healthy depress an
expectant don't expect that's not going to cost
and Holland Miguel if Mike the study all
his life of Jim broadcasts every day
makes mistakes scripts you have to be
honest with you but if well in the
next year with me
and he tells me in my marriage is
improving
before we fought every day when we were already
week with fire now one day a week
we fight over water and champagne and I'm
going to say wow incredible and how true it is that they
are improving that is the best
offering to the teacher when
you be kampeter when you
become teachers imagine
humanism don't think about money
[Music]
my song of chimbacalle touch
can teach in the simple  Not
needing a big hotel in Thailand,
Mike, there's a transformation, and if they don't have
money, I've been teaching for many years in my
car because it's okay. It has to be
Quintín Segundo Down Experian, I
inspected myself, don't expect everyone to respect you
and then cause big problems,
Mike, that students are like children, we
love them and they create many problems, the
students are causing problems,
Siller Télam,
peace of Kameni with Firework,
the company boss can run to the
Oscars, they go to the bad workers, but
the mother can't run to the airs, I fired them, go away, you don't
work anymore, they
connect, it's a job of, it's obvious,
these older adults know that
some don't grow after 65 years old,
but you can't fire them, studies or
the students too, after you
start studying, it's indisputable that
you start teaching a student group, you can't
fire them, they're disrespectful, they
respect you,
if then they give you problems all day,
then the job of the gay extract and
Mike is life is
stone, no, no, don't have expectations that
Michael's life is what they are,
everyone is very nice with that, the  All
this is also like that, Mom's job is
very difficult, she never sleeps, she's always
worried, it's the same as being a teacher. Do
n't think you're going to become
someone very famous, don't expect that, it's a lot of
work,
but come on,
and Mom knows it's the sweetest job, being a
teacher is the best job in the world,
Mom's job.
People ask me if I'm just
thinking about the country, what's your advice?
Number 1
is the hardest job in the world,
number 2
is the happiest life you can have. In
Latin, Javier, there's nothing that makes you
happier. Number 1, justification: more difficult,
we show many problems,
use a lot, if the children create
problems, the students even more,
but there's no better job. I've done it
all my life and I'm extreme
when I have problems raising
funds,
please give me money, we don't have
money
quickly, but people tell me you're happy, I am.
This is the best job in the
world, the happiest job in the world. I fear
Beijing more, Victor, but the motivation
must be pure, trustworthy, do
n't hesitate to chew on the motivation to
be pure, don't expect that you're going to become
famous, don't expect that people are going to
give you, do
n't have an expectation of respect  90% is going to
be a problem, the students' minds
told me, he says happily, it's worth not having
done the best there is
and for the moment
[Music]
that's the warehouse back there, one of the
red buildings is the university, so I
want to buy that one
and we see on YouTube
[Music]
ok Aitor, I
already showed them to YouTube,
they have the 122
and it's
habitable,
$100, I already showed them
and successfully,
not the
same garbage, different packages, they are
all an angel, it's close to you
[Music]
new winds in the spicy,
the publishing house, there will be angels in every
country, not exactly
what topics we are on,
what topic are we talking about
inside, the one
you like, if you teach
even your family in the kitchen,
all the Buddhas are going to be present and they are going
to check, taught very well, taught the
pen very well and nitties, so when
you teach the Buddhas they are going to go, it smells
good, it's a sweet aroma,
they are like bees, you are like honey,
they understand, make up and make the happy
ones, when you return home, teach the
pen to your family, to your friends, this
Especially if your friend is struggling
with our husband on signs of where
actions or critical input are coming from, of
course they're going to improve on point, but
more importantly, the Buddhas are going to sell
because they like to hear someone
pointing with actors. My old students,
when they teach the pen, fall asleep, but
while they're asleep, all the Buddhas
come to listen.
So I feel very happy because
I need a couple of microphones, we're going to
do questions and answers,
and so you're holding on.
[Applause]
Everyone, everyone, we're going
to see if the one I
told her in Russian is taken care of, that she has to take her
husband to dinner with the $100.
Now, from Christian, in question,
a moment, what does Ibiza ask?
He's going to decide.
[Music]
My question is, what are they teaching us
to see all people as a Buddha?
But there's also a teaching in the
sutra that you should stay away from
people who behave badly. We as
new students, we must make him
happy. There are two types of friends,
Victor, little hooks, we call them. Dictator, I
thought of YouTube fiction,
they come to your house and we go to the cafe
to  Review the kingdom of Thailand,
I'm just saying let's have coffee and let's have
dessert and let's enjoy
together.
U2, we call them Tetro, also friend of the
Dharma,
they're sitting in the same room.
Let's go to the cinema. It's for mobile. There's a
Spider movie, plus cost in the arc.
Let's go on the ship.
Let's watch this movie. Good joke.
I went to see it
in Shanghai with tongue.
At that moment you
have the choice. There are two friends in the
room.
One tells you, let's review my plan. Ring
at the gym, cow at Starbucks, and
defense. And the other friend tells you, camera
is kitchen. Let's watch the movie. Up to
that moment, the second
friend
is like a demon.
Thank you to the second friend. I mean,
thank you. I like the movie. In
Guatemala, maybe we can go tomorrow. There's
this vice candidate who said
we should relax.
[Music] He
also went to see the movie for TV,
but this video is supposed to be
reviewed well. It stands out for waist or
not.
The second person is a donkey. If they
're testing you, Harting is
testing him. Check.
They're checking if you're a good
student or not
on Wii, so this week a new
champion,
a Buddha, will appear to you as your husband
and he's going to yell at you. He wants to check you out. Did you learn
anything in Thailand? Want to be
mine? He wants to remember. Don't think that
all doubts are very good.
Trouble the new line. You learn more from
problems than from new problems.
To the person who gives you problems, and if I'm
not teaching much,
when we don't have problems we don't
remember emptiness.
When we have problems we remember
emptiness.
I saw two guys, maybe those people
who create problems often, but maybe they
aren't, or in fact they don't know how to
position themselves. They could be doubts, they could
be no more,
but it helps us more if we think they are
hoaxes. It's Friday, so be it. I don't
need this husband that I like. He's
Buddha.
Maybe the smell of the night, and if it's
possible, yes,
this height. If they are mute and yell at you so that
you think about emptiness, well
possible for you is not enough.
That's logical. And Tom Hardy, you don't have to
say more than a year and he accepted. My
husband is definitely a  Buddha who
told him is true
and not in the voice but in our flattery
but at our level
we can yes we can honestly say he
can be vulgar and figure in a 10
respect now if he is a Buddha and he lacks it
in respect then you do very bad
karma that adapts and I can tell
a story
I was in the diamond business
for 19 years individual no individual
inning of cable who doesn't know or know web
finally at the beginning the company couldn't
pay me salary I worked gravitated sometimes we
couldn't make the day of mbang that
the Stalin law we couldn't pay
the salaries of the debutant me and you
take Stalin next week
they would come with me well you
can have your salary the
following week
sometimes six weeks they can't stop
after we became the
biggest diamond company in wounded
and the pay of incredible nothing
huffman and I would give him half of the measure
and the title is directly to the manual
without taxes illegal enemy of Bottega
Majesty so they take half of
my salary abysmal tangent last and
every six months I had to go to my boss
to you
I mean you owe me one hundred  I have two hundred thousand
dollars,
internet, TV, picket line, stage,
now you have to give a check,
seriously, to Madrid, I was already saying how much I had,
my song,
I was saying 200,000, let my, it has to be
done, 300,000, and what they extradited me to, they gave me
100,000 euros, it was like,
wow, incredible, thank you, this
stop, monastery,
thank you,
and he did it for deeds,
finally he gave me a large amount of
extra money,
you wondered, to ask a personal question, were they
all Jewish, are you
from Israel?
It's a clue,
Louis, like, are they
all really Jewish?
Because the extra money to the Buddhist monastery,
each time he makes a great song,
we lead the tasks because he does the
set, and one said, William, discover, you
never know which religion is right, it's possible
the Jews are right, it's
possible the Christians have to,
possibly the Muslims have the
weeks of Vizcaya, possibly your
monastery in tax gifts, a
smart person of the same
age,
after you die, it was
very funny, Miami, without us, we
have known, and a year, the people who have a
list, the people who create problems, we don't
know, green to upload on your website, it's
better to be respectful with  Everything
is perhaps mute, perhaps it greets, we don't know
its donation to many religions, both
live, some may be wrong, but it's
not a problem to
respect a person who is not a Buddha,
nor is it a problem to respect a
person and find out that they are not a Buddha,
anyway you make a good seed
[Music]
so respect then it is safer
than a sample of donations, it is
safer,
another question
[Applause]
[Music] you
told me that when you are
teaching in a cafe that all the doubters
come to see
because we create things for
our friends,
doubt comes from their own side of
our seed in champions, and this is
the second chapter of the fiscal galiana
with a path, that chapter is called going and
coming and just going and coming, if they come
because I have to ask them what
avenger I have to
ask them to come, when the
Buddha comes, he comes from you, that it is only your
path, so there are two ways of
coming, of arriving, still a child, but it's okay, what
law of both I'm going to give you, I
live in a small town and what is it
called, Ramis River, a very small motor
in China, it makes me Chinese  New York, which
is a small town,
this is true,
Jamaica, you see, well, even more so, but my town
is super small, I think we have three
thousand people in my town,
let's choose maybe, and we have one
post office and there are two ladies
who work there, I think they're about 90
years old, and you write a letter, there's
a little bell ringing, I think they
're sleeping in the back, and they
arrive walking very slowly,
they take the letters and send the letter by
post, it takes me 15
minutes to get to the post office,
if I write a letter to be
Michael and I take it to the
post lady, this letter
is addressed to me, two weeks, it's going to take
two weeks so I can walk
in 15 minutes, put in this, let's
say, write the anonymous letter
to gays and Michael and Superior Phantom,
you're very silly, you're a fan, and I
put it in an envelope and give it
to the old lady on the way, after two weeks
it's going to arrive in Stoner's Currents where I
think the son of the old ladies is, I
also walk  He's going to give the envelope in
authority, I'm going to open it. You say it's
the Phantom, and I know it's the air. It's
Franklin. You're a fool. The question was, should I be
angry with the mailman who
brought me the letter? Sorry, or not,
he didn't write the letter, he just delivered it.
Her husband is the mailman, and you wrote
the letter.
He just delivered the letter. Audio: When your
husband fights with you,
he's delivering your own
seeds. If your husband criticizes you, who
wrote the letter? And I did it, you did it. Don't kill the mailman, he
just delivered your own letter. When your
husband criticizes you, he's just a mailman, and
Di Natale didn't write the letter. You
wrote the letter. They have White, who's the one in
charge because the gay guy is being
talked to about this. Santi, for me,
some people ask me
[Music],
for example, when I take an aspirin,
I get a headache. I take an aspirin,
that doesn't work, or not.
Saints, sometimes, and view of other people
with the end,
if you helped other people with their
headache in the past, yes,
you planted the seed so that the
medicine works
So meditation,
so if medicine is going to work
for you, sorry, if you've ignored your
friends who have had headaches,
then when you take aspirin it's not
going to work, okay, okay, I mean, yoga is just like
yoga, like this, no agent
who does yoga and if they get strong, they're
wine, Tannat anchors, others take the same
class and get hurt,
the class is the postman and the aspirin is
the postman, give it to you,
sister, they didn't write the law,
the letter,
I understand Windows and Mac, when you're in
the chimba Cannes teaching
and you're teaching the pen, also
beauty with you and may the Buddhas come to you,
endeavour, scan to you and may the Buddhas come with
you, did the Buddhas come with you
with toys and issues, don't
forget the three questions, number one,
I have a pen in my hands and give me your
number two, of reason
in image, which champion, and I have a
pen in my hand that comes from me,
number three, in the field there is a pen, my
hand that comes from the pen, no, no way, it
is TP-Link, it will lead when you teach of
the pen in the simm bacchanal  Starwood, that's
going to come, the Buddha
will come because they come from your seeds. Yes,
some wood will come when you invoke it, when
you teach to prove that it doesn't come from you.
But was it the Buddha? And teeth, don't
forget these three questions, always
ask these three questions, you won't get
confused.
And if there's a feather in my hand, if I'm
just now, I love them, and the animal feather doesn't
come from me. If this stupid champion
pende, the first hand comes from the feather,
not this pure field of cobisa. Be careful
if the Buddha takes coffees from your seeds. No,
impossible.
Yesterday we studied all the volunteers,
and the impossible topic is the 8 impossibles,
which is that it doesn't mean it can't
happen.
No, it doesn't come from your seeds. One more question.
Well,
add it
and that's it. A
whole,
how I
just wanted to clarify the question
because seeds create our world,
but the world is,
the world comes from my seeds. How
can they influence others? They are waters in
good, in purees. I wasn't born as Buddhists
because of Christine, just as a Christian. My man
without borders, we were
four brothers and my mom
took us to church.
I enjoyed the church, it was very beautiful.
I still go sometimes.  Months
in the same school, when it was the same
church, when I was a child,
I recognize the smell, I like the prayer, it's
very similar to maturing, and here I am.
My mom would take us to church, she would tell us, in essence, we
would say, in Buddhism, we cross our
legs,
in Christianity, we were children, Pencahue
in mind, my mom would say, put your hands like this,
and we would put our hands, close your
eyes, we would close our eyes and
think of everyone in the world,
think of all beings in the world, you're a
fan, and who isn't?
The child is doing well, he's going to believe in his
mom, and that's how he thinks of all that, it's
difficult, a joke, and then she said, pray
for everyone, on the
tablet, the
happening,
think of helping everyone, we are
understanding that sometimes we get
older, children believe everyone is
lucky, when we get older we no longer
believe that the young mom can't
help everyone in the world, go well and
everyone, I know,
besides, I'm going to need it, if you
understand, I'm going to give you a few minutes, I
am, and there is no sleep, and they trained me in
Bayamón for my mom,
at least to think of everyone in the world,
when I turned 20 I said, Mom, it's not
possible that  Form what's right for
little kids, but when you grow up it's
not possible, Mom, to
change the whole world. One person
can't change the world at night.
You become a
cynical person. It's amazing, it's not possible to jump.
I'm super Scioli, just like a
few years ago. If I hadn't been, they would have taught Norway.
You met Christian
last year, the one Ford seems to act to
justify. I
hate him. They
explain he's too handsome,
but well, he's also very muscular. He
's one of the richest families
in Norway. There are three reasons
why. One is because he has hair like...
Name your number two, strong. This is
none. Number three is super rich. He has the
best. The worst thing about physics, Whitney
Mais, is that he's super nice. It's
difficult.
Her country
teaches about a young man in class.
Oswald Kabakov said, "I have a girlfriend,
Watson." Before me,
I want someone to give me a kiss, so I
came to your class. Now I understand what to do.
There's a famous restaurant. Not only do many
people go there, but
tonight,
I'm going to the restaurant. Something that is
ambiguous and indirect. I'm going to...  kiss all
the women in the restaurant on the rise and I'm
going to plant the seventh golf in tourism
to find my girlfriend who will kiss me on
web migration and I said no no no no wait wait
wait for those women
also have many is that really
this is not right
that it should be the same
if you want a partner and unity plan and end
you have to plant an area
if you want to plant a seed for the
universe you need to find one
this lonely one I have different
suggestions if you find an old lady
with and once a week and movie
takes her to the cinema and slugging she is alone
maybe she doesn't have family to visit her the
cinema plan and you are going to plant a seed
cofrentes and then you are going to find your
girlfriend sodena and you have to move it I'm going to
return to tilt about six weeks
after I left to fungible she sent me an
email just like I took the
old lady
to the cinema to clients and I planted a seed I
have a girlfriend I like this system
has they are ready now six maintain
six months later there is cat and child
I had a next one and there is no video it
should be the video lasts two minutes
videos again in languages
The video is the Norwegian not paying attention that I do
n't know what they're talking about. That
Chinese Chinese Chinese Chinese administration
means going to the cinema. Movie. I'm not going
to teach you a word in Chinese. It
means going to the cinema in Norway. Now
you
artificial ones with him. He sent me this video
six months after I met his
girlfriend. YouTube.
You tell me what the video is
and the sun.
[Music]
how
and god
yes no
[Music]
hate
yes
well
[Music]
and no no
d
9.
This video is shown on television
every week.
The video is turned off by the national
telephone company on cable -9 and the
Norwegian government in Excel and it says
the end and I tello don't seem to have another
sense. Mobile. If the young man takes the
old man, alternates, no telephone. Change
camp ifo by the national
telephone company and the government will pay for
both tickets.
[Applause]
Nine questions  The question is,
how did this video start, hand in town,
the ancient art that has detected very
well,
hundreds of thousands of young people are
taking hundreds of thousands of elderly people
to the cinema, how did it start? I'm going to be there, me and
Matiko, who only know the boy who
decided not to go kiss all the girls,
restoring, for example, being honest with
him, a person in You Want Is Good
Friends,
the
YouTube tube, five years, if it doesn't exist,
implant the seed in the aid of the
elderly, then his friend had, then the friend of the friend, the
friend of the friend of the friend of the friend
had a girlfriend,
Foresters Fainas, a virus of the four
steps 9 spread through Norway from one
person after, to have all the people,
so there are two ways to teach
all the people who put said
language, you can sit in the church,
condition, I wish I could help the
campus, you can do and Tingüindín is
good and is being, kind, is serious and doesn't
help people directly but
indirectly is very good and
indirectly is good, or just do, by
Steve Jobs of USA, the four steps, the
viruses themselves, connect your, become
someone successful, are financially and
become someone healthy
I have a beautiful relationship, a
happy marriage, and then your friends are going to copy you,
and the friend of a friend of a friend is going to
copy you. The friend of a friend of a friend of a friend
in bed,
Lewis, the government is going to be a movie, and
you're probably in the star position.
When you understand
the best thing you can do is be a friend to
help everyone, and then you
use the four steps at the same time and
option. You become someone
successful,
and people are going to copy you, and it's possible to
help the whole world.
Every person has the power and
attitude that you have to take and position yourself to become
successful. You have
a good marriage, sweet and healthy
tweets. Sign up, anpe time is
human advertising. Do you understand?
Thank you very much.
[Music] [
Applause]